All.
Going to Go taken him down no just
a fixed income and more expense How
do you think he'll take it like
a soldier my life my soldier no ketchup
this is the worst last meal I ever had
Sorry just his words. All sure glad to
see you weren't so they going to K.
Through the studio I knew we would is
a really good guy sorry Jackson awaits
my governor yelling out sorry. No.
No we're. No word
and well. I don't know who to
vote for next time I'm on jacks.
I suppose. Also that said. When
I take
a look I wouldn't advise
it you get so bored. I
. Guess I haven't even put in electricity.
Jackson I'm going to grant you a
special privilege not often given to
a menu position is what you asked for
a chance to go to the newspaper to. Begin
to go off your chest Thanks for so
you know well Jack's. I'll be right
here. To Jackson I think you're
wonderful you've really
got what it takes exactly
a cream cigarette or my
thanks George might be
a song that. Well you got what I call
God by the way I figured anybody got
a match. The way I figured if a guy
feels in his heart he's taking
a phony rap Well it's not so tough to kick
the bucket it's not so tough to walk to
the last mile it's just tough to light
a cigarette that's all. They jack I
had to get into this mess without
one so as
a woman. You should have seen this woman
skin likes musette beautiful blue eyes
dark silken hair kind of
a gal that make you want to give away
your last shirt. I borrowed this from the
ward that's good and you made it you come
out the office did you fall in love with
her wait
a minute one of the time you may not know
this but I wasn't always the type of
before they pin this murder rap on me I
had one of the sweetest little rackets in
San Francisco
a legitimate business that of the legitimate
was profitable my office was in the
Trafalgar building just on the edge of
Chinatown Oh in China Oh not right in you
know California speed on the Hill in fact
I'm. Coming down the hill on the cable
car you just see my on. Third
floor front. Ronnie with the name
Ronnie maybe five hundred I'll never forget
that day for two hours I've been trying
to make that little brat smile I threw the
book at him every surefire trick in the
train.
This kid's going to grow up to be
a sponsor. Even wearing out the light. I
want somebody to watch the Bernie.
Another masterpiece we don't
care for. Your wonderful two Mr
Jackson Well that's because I was
a kid once myself.
I'm just dying to see those crews will
they be ready all the first thing in the
morning to spawn and I'm sure you're
like wow. You little rascal you.
Time. Doesn't need
a whole. Happy little girl maybe.
Baby. For
a two fisted He-Man like Randy Jackson.
Promised to have pictures of the kids ready
by morning so I got to work and. Must've
been about twenty minutes later far some
my dad when I heard a door slam in the
hallway outside I knew it was Sam
a cloud coming back to his office from
a busy day fitting the goods in a few
a sort of. Sandwich the coolest toughest
private eye in the business you see I
wanted to be a detective It
only took brains courage and
a gun and I had. Figured out
a way for Sam to hire me so I started
across the hall already I could see my name
in big letters Ronnie Jackson's
private eye what I didn't see was
a small print underneath rest in peace.
For catching
a rather. High sand. Couple
of guns with it you think. To
talk over somebody know one
of the most warm fun of being
a match is about. So I don't
mind running that's just not
how I mean looks and it came to the
license and everything now can I be your
partner I told you before stick to watching
the burden you. Oh yeah but I was kind
of up for this kind of life
all my life I want to be
a hard boiled detective like Humphrey
Bogart or Dick Powell or even how to land.
You know have those beautiful women coming
into the office and those warm fires on
those rainy nights that's a
kind of life I want how about
a sad. Smooth
. So I can be a lot of help the same Look
here's my latest invention right here
a camera with
a keyhole lens takes pictures right through
doors I've been kicked out of five
hotels already. How about it's Am I
going to work for you just give me
a simple YES or NO NO. No but that's
too simple why don't you give
a little thought I'm going to Chicago for
a few days. And leave the door I'm
saying come to an end of the phone.
I could go with the I've got a cold
just like that I can help you out quite
a bit take your money he will work are.
You sure there's nothing I can do for you
now you've given us clean. That's
the last chance I'll give him.
Keep my nose clean answer the phone. I had
a going business for myself.
Ronnie Jackson the private eye. I
could touch those guns up top souls over
a warm fire even if it wasn't
raining. As much as he can.
Move.
It.
If.
It. For I
suppose you wonder why I want to have
a girl comes in here does that. I need
a detective please say that you help
me look I'm just I please Mr MacLEOD.
Just common sense. This is
my type of case. My name is
come on. There in
a month. There. Are
a few of us someone's watching you know
that's me food. But I am right here
three days ago the queen of Peru with
about my husband or you got to has been.
This was taken the day
we arrived at the club
a couple San Francisco so that they must
rate I'm in trouble deep trouble What's
the wheelchair for my husband is an invalid
he hasn't been out of the wheelchair in
seven years you're in trouble
he talking. At the dock.
I want to have to clear our luggage through
customs I was gone five ten minutes at
the most when I returned he had disappeared
snatched or you got to the place you
know. If I go to the police
they're killing food.
That's what I want you to find
out. Look I have no money but this
ring can be pawned anywhere for at least
five thousand dollars. Looks just
a five grams
a lot of moves you know going into nothing
we Montaser generous if you will just
find my husband I will be all
right. You. Bring the match
over this isn't necessary. It's not
this and they must find me here for one
hundred here anything to get the gift.
As soon as you can. Five
minutes be too soon.
Dangerous Man. Be careful. Not to know
you are detained Don't worry your pretty
head about it honey I find your
husband cool and I still. Come in.
Contact with your life.
What you made oh oh I'm sorry.
Jim in the studio sometime
after hours now take your picture when
everybody's gone no charge. Except the
negatives nobody.
Pressured on at any time.
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR YOU want to be
a detective don't you.
See what's an address.
A map my life.
It's.
A.
Small village. I think this your
camera on me. Let's say you don't
have to pull the gun on me to
kiss me any time. I was on my own this
NG has been in the dark I dream boat
up to a gorgeous lip service from what
a pilot and oh yeah that mysterious man
the whole thing just like you'd read
a detective magazine I had my car for the
address the doll gave me that turns out
this place is practically
a sleeper jump from town anyway later that
afternoon when I'm driving through the
gates of one of those upper bracket estates
down in the. Pretty soon I come to
another game that should have been
my cue to put the time. And I got
a lot of the mansion on
a joint must have been something left
over from weathering heights you know the
kind of
a house it looks like you can find whale
in the hallways I didn't know it then but
I was going to be the quail.
Well maybe that is so
beautiful. It is day though.
But it's like sort of.
I mean. For director
mind are good afternoon good up in
the queues met Yes various Mondays
expecting me. For years one to come and.
I share a place for the free
money down Eric's here but I'm
a harmless you know living. Out Your Never
mind I'll take it from me with your old
. Airport see your comic rough if.
You Thanks couples. Very amusing.
Lol.
Pretty funny. Yes pretty
but you were so anxious.
These. Low down.
On Oh really honed. To
a dream. Many
Chronos. Due.
TO is no more. Monsoon.
Like. First and I know that I am and with
the predicting Oh you can get as close as
you like. We're not together I'm with you
to my dying breath Please you're not
leaving fingerprints. I am bearing
my name in this country Iraq
yes I thought you said the guy was
your husband. I. I had to help
I know man somehow they always seem to be
more interested in the problems of young
wives with older cars. And all it just
seems that way to you please let.
My uncle came to this country out there
you put me so important that he wouldn't
tell anyone about it not even me your
uncle so he's not your husband well did I
quote you any rights I may work cheap or
you know please not now too fast OK But
tell me did your uncle have any
enemies not that I know of.
And how about this house Pulitzer it
belonged to a major Simon Montague he was
a former business partner the Baron and
my uncle disappeared I was frantic So I
call major Marty you and he offered to
help me. And what do you know about it my
uncle trusted him implicitly
and still. He treats me like
a child tells me not to worry says
that he's handling. It all the time I
feel as though I'm being watched.
And he's been so sweet and kind
ever since my arrival it's kind of dark
and. All we were just talking about you
something flat RUMOLD. Maybe our children
this is over that if there's anything
warms my heart it's fine are people like
me as much as I like them I don't believe
I'm here they are set Oh well Mr Craig
Oh heartless CRAIG LAPSLEY and I thought
your name was great I'm
great too that's quite
a coincidence I did make him out of you
when I met Mr Craig on shipboard. I'm still
a little seasick It's
a pleasure no news or anything are going
to follow our view of the country you just
speak up Thanks Aaron. You have
a cigar No thanks I'm driving I prayed.
And when I heard that name before.
I went down to the front
call for you please take
a message for all the lot of it may
be important. You're quite right.
It's given. All right.
Now we're quit playin possum. How
do you do Mr MacLEOD about how I.
Crave the name of trade. How
the shepherds. Are you know
the you're
a private detective Oh yes yes yes same
just common sense. And just to show you my
heart's in the right place
I'm going to help you do
a little detective OK there's ways
that come in there. I'm going to have
a little surprise for you. Two
partners gentleman this is Mr
MacLEOD MacLeod I'd like you to meet the
man in the picture there man tell me how
do you do but she she said you've been
snatched you have my word for that young man
I'm not
a mirage. Which told me she
seems so i don't get such
a lovely girl the very slow young woman.
That Dr can tell you about her I believe
you met the doctor. Oh yes we had
a long talk outside beautiful day isn't
it I said that when Mr MacLEOD as you
perhaps know it is not the habit of
a psychiatrist to put on display the skeleton
in anyone's family closets However I
believe you when entitled to an explanation
of the strange behavior to abandon
Montes right why but she just told
me she was as nice last week she was
a little sister not funny major. For the
past six months Miss Monti has been
suffering from an acute form of schizophrenia
accompanied by visual aberrations and
increasingly severe paranoid
delusions. And how she mentally.
Mr MacLEOD is
a Harvard man I am not
paramount high Cleveland. I
just think if I had a case all
make it easy on yourself I had
a lot of these. This month has an
obsession that her own life is in
danger and she believes that her uncle the
baton here has been kidnapped Well gee I
I mean why don't you bring our inherent
show of the bear. Hell that's what I do and
. It would be to see the
show. My ideas to break down
have suggested stand up. Or does
she snap
a cap very often I mean when you invite
company for dinner do you take away
a knife and fork she's only dangerous if
she's emotionally disturbed you must come
across many similar cases in your business
Mr MacLEOD. Me all show or show I can
take those good souls or leave alone and
usually I leave alone I figure that. Well
I must get back to the office
and file some thing else I'm
a bigger Prince. You know my heart
goes out for sure that girl.
Is all mixed up it's downright.
Some bottom out the map
she even gave you want to hold for
mysterious map missing girl pretty corny you
know there was something about the way she
looked at made me suspicious the way she
looked I didn't care what you kept them
at all sure why not she may not have been
up here but hubba hubba.
Thank you did. You
watch yourself son.
Come in go out of their
nutty as
a fruitcake and with all that beautiful
frosting. Are just saying go for it Mr
great at any time he's in the neighborhood
he should feel free to drop the I'm
having to live with us. You all excuse
me all don't go major you know the old
saying Three's Company into the crowd
you take aerials out yeah. Well.
Here we are alone at last goodbye do you
know who that phone calls from the Polish
. Our first good soul is
about to friend here.
Why did I get up today. I just
spoke to my uncle that's funny so
why who my uncle are known to
me he told me not to worry
but I'm terribly December. Motional
and yes. He said he would say
Oh he's safe all right. I mean he's safe
all right but he's not sick I know we
all know he's
a terrible spot but I feel he's in great
danger Yash Yes he's in great danger yeah
but you say for the record he said you
sound like an umpire Don't you see
someone forced him to make that call someone
who wants me to believe that nothing
is wrong. Oh Mr MacLEOD I don't know what
to do I'm at my wits and there's no high
pass there an hour ago. You told me his
sister you better take the ring back
but. Mr Macleod said you wouldn't
desert me. Not now no no I just
remembered I got a date with J.
Edgar Hoover I can never makes
a move without me but I always did where
in this thing together you said you'd
stick with me to your dying breath and I'm
getting too close to it now don't get
upset Miss Monte you just
listen to the major He's
a very fine man and he likes you oh so
they've been talking to you they did
telling you things or you're crazy I mean
you're being silly Nobody's been talking
to me I haven't been talking to myself Oh
yes they have they told you something and
you believe it all no no I'm I'm on your
side oh well now I know who is at the
bottom of all this may just Simon Monjack
you oh no no we're in this together baby
we're please don't believe in. Please
and you'll help me please. Please baby.
Do it. Mama knows best.
Going promise me you'll guard the map
of your life and share them. Map.
The math. Here let me take this oh.
You're going to the mailman later
gee the six o'clock about what I. Saw.
From my car when I realized me and my get
parted company holster and I figured
little Miss groove almost to lift it when
she kissed me started to go back for it
but I changed my mind I spot
a high wind around the corner of the
house and decide to climb up and take
a gander I think the only way to get the
inside dope is from the outside dope so I
scamper up the hill in about three
jumps like any other ghost take
a sneak peek and what do you know the guy
who told me he couldn't walk is out of
his wheelchair and sashaying
around chipper as
a jaybird then I knew Colorado was once
I get out my Brownie and I'm all set to
snap Exhibit A When laughing boy gets out
of his chair and starts for the window I
figure he sees me but no he pulls up the
shade right my chest like it was ladies
night in the Turkish bath
I'm stymied only for
a second. Here's where my gadget pays off
the greatest invention since the Albany
night boat this will do it I says Next
stop rogues gallery. Pretty quick.
Car Lot of. Publicity.
Shots apparent just a fixture
a picture a camera for take
a hard on me right there
he goes. All right.
He wanted to.
Change just.
Too fast for. Romney. Last year with
him taking the other road trip.
And I am back right alongside you.
Calling this jelly this jelly
just coming. You. Can become.
A man any man you know what
a man he must be getting.
Finance coming. To
be honest remember the satirist.
To tell your your mom.
Didn't think you'd do it after that bet
we hear you doll you we both came through
like men.
Well
a lot better get me the
state police Yeah. But
here I get some of the old.
Couples.
Operating never mind
a car. Very
thoughtful of your to
think through and get it.
And I came to I was playing
post office in the floor I had
a lump on my head the size of my head inside
Tuscany was conducting the Enron cars
with real black men to look at the bottle
of old tile driver in the sun the same
thing the nub of. Those kids with
a hammer started pounding against the
something was in my head it was somebody
knocking on the door and it wasn't the
crowd star it was my door my door and the
other room. Watched you
yes here I am Mr Jackson
my head trying to come out
yes for even now Mr Jackson
a man of your responsibility shouldn't
drink well who's drink and I'm all that
that's
a bottle of being Bob or I want
my baby pictures. Picture. Oh
wait a minute where you going just
a second this is just what.
I got on it's gone let me
see I had here and I took it and there the
step is just don't hold up Miss fungus
not your baby's picture here's
an item that have a have
a developer in it some place else place
our model doesn't just mean I'm retired
remember that if you have another baby
place. While I'm thinking well I've got
things to do yes sir important
things to do. But I got to do.
Quite
a lot of. Hey
there is. One of the gang All right
what you do with come clean your
guns so we mean business fellas. What's
going on here don't try to look so innocent
with. That I got
a knife. What you think
I was last night except
a mom tried to prove me. Wrong I want
to hear about the name of. A lot
of. Who she is she staying here with major
money. This house belongs to the George
Graham and they've been in South America
before months six months yet he subletting
. Take
a look inside please come along to me.
I'll show you they're probably all hide.
This looks like nobody home nothing personal
about that I hope what do you think I
think a rebuke is in order on I wait
a minute don't get your badges in an uproar
you've got this all wrong they fix my
car they fix they get the best everything
that's directed to try to make people
think everybody's crazy I haven't had
a head start you gotta listen to me you
gotta trust me fellas this is the biggest
frame up. Thank you. Dr back
to town Yeah well let me tell you
something what I like long drives.
Bothers again I personally punch you in the
nose started to look like other people
. Might be worth. You not
a bad guy performer but I'm
going to be. Starting from the.
President. Alone but.
If. You.
Cling on to the back you know you know
what to do we're not going to let you move
why did he come back why does he want to
search the house looking for clues. That
he wants
a clue to call out of where ours see
that he finally won this one. And
.
Always look so easy in
those tires to accuse.
Me.
Of.
Even. More.
Pain. And.
During. Seen live. That's
where. I believe
a clue. Here
high.
Well I knew where the dollars my next move
is to find or so I get back into my hot
rod special and start up
about an hour later I spot
a sign of the cliff lodge told when to
locate the girl pretending I'm just another
guest looking for
a little quiet like station and the place
is just what I figured pretty some
restorative sleep with call for. Barmaid
how to get to the lodge where I was
just as where I live where there is
a chemist all partly. Did you notice if
a good looking dark haired girl
checked in there last night.
Here to play these last three holes will
take you right there. OK but how about my
car. Covered in the name.
Of mine's Smithers.
Nine I guess you'd first OK. This girl last
night did you notice if she was alone.
To make a small wager dollar
a hole All right thank you
notices. You know for night.
Mr Cup must move me. Like
a pretty good rounded
almost well to do. Like
I got over those straps.
All right I like up.
I can see that thanks. For that
I didn't think you had
a ball down plughole boy
the only one down. Where
is your ball right here. I fly.
Right on the green and I can't even see
the green I care. About that but I owe
you
a roll. Nice racket you got thanks. For
staying here you know all the room next to
mine keeps me up all night long playing
Yankee doodle on the spike of key. Why
don't you tell paternal about it.
You were really up quite glad now they go
oh I'm lookin for you chummy we going to
see the doctor Dr. Sanitarium you
got me wrong I'm not crazy I
know I know maybe you'd like someone that
much once you have those nurses true to
notice so I want you but I'm OK I'm saying
our property was this coordination.
It's wrong here and
it's. Well our practice
a little See you later come on easy that's
my pinball hand we're going to see the
doctor it's no use but I'm not all
up let's see the doctor. Oh Oh
what shall we never get that down again.
That's better that's as apartments and.
Things like this could be
permanent. Couples. So
they have bellhops are welcome to
seek. Calisthenics. Home study
a map with
a map. Very bad luck I didn't expect
to see you get me out of the same.
Very bad trying to talk somebody look I
don't know what's going on here and I'm not
scared see you got company man
cut out of me. I was there
nine that's all right baby why did I have
to go and do this now I've got you in
this mess to. Now wait
a minute don't go feminine on
me. Don't go masculine either.
Oh I didn't know this was going to be
formal So I would be right with your boss.
Mullins said that. You
were not going to have
a little talk yeah I'll do the talking
you do the set. I'll do that it's all.
Out of the set and the matches man
can have it on now. I've got to
change things that's changed Sam All
right recently I offered to buy
a pair Monday the mineral rights of the
section of his land option to lay the
balance on my own who didn't know
he came to this country to make
a deal with somebody else who is this someone
else and what kind of mineral rights
you're getting too inquisitive
and that ain't healthy now maybe
a little color here begin to see the light
you know I'm very fond of Carlotta and I
don't like to see you holdin out on
me lay off are you phony. You all
the good thing you're here I'd
be brutal. For. Uncle's death.
You were wrong to have they haven't how
to make here is that your uncle he looks
just like the guy in the picture I took
he sure and on. That picture I might
respond everything for us like
a specialist. But salmon if you don't
mind I'd like to acquaint the Baron with
a few basic facts if you miss your
liberal we have you we have your means
and having Mr MacLEOD we have to
match that judge you haven't.
Spent. Before the Chrysanthemum
rooms we will have it
pleased with this OK yes it's all
right I've stopped all around
I want that map and I want it now what you
want what you're going to get are two
different things are not the
given time are not all of the.
Term punk is my stamp don't be so rough was
fair you can take it the poor boy's see
he don't know what's gone on. It's all
oh I'm sorry honey I didn't mean to
get so fresh. Oh it's you home. Now
where's the map son how is that what you
want or why did you say so you don't have
to get at the heart of what I say don't
what's the use they'll beat it out of the
Senate way we might as well tell them Go
on chummy you tell them all right I had
the map in
a water cooler in my office he's lying I've
searched his face now you looked in the
wrong watercooler the one I mean is
a thing. We might as well tell me.
You'll find the map in the water cooler
at the Ferry Building. Yeah yeah the Ferry
Building and the water cooler by the
newsstand third cup from the top we'll
find out tonight if you're taking about
three hours to get to the Ferry
Building and back is gone charm. Dr. To
register them as patients in case A They
should happen to meet where they're an
accident the usual papers will be filled
out to see if Tony doesn't happen to find
that map.
Changed.
Van. Dam can eat me. What's up maybe
a cigarette you saw me taken
my uncle it was a message in
a tranny We've two hours to get out of here
all we've got nothing to worry about to
Tony gets back. You know they took all my
clothes mine too they did what they did
how. Are you going to help him. And this
is no time to be thinking about your looks
here good. So how'd you know about that
cigarette My uncle never snuck
down when he asked me for
a night. He wanted to get in touch
with James Caan or engineering Corp.
I've seen this done thousand times it was
a strange town. We got going here so I was
so simple just put the happen in Iraq
give it
a quick twist to let out the money and get
up we can play jacks later in the morning
. Question vanished
a quick. Oh
I feel OK take me away because I've
run into some drug I fixed it all
myself although I haven't got much
of an appetite if I could take
a long long haul all of them there guys
wouldn't let you you know show me I ask you
where you got
a funny way of showing us I'm still trying
to get the car puzzles to move back in
I'm sorry but. You just don't
know your own strength.
You know Willy I like you
to. You dude yes there was
a physique Boulder Dam with legs and look
at those shoulders and that arm like
a sack
a door knob recess recess to reach sets
you just turning the page show me.
Your muscles to. Look
around is there some place.
All there it is. It's just like
a womb. Easy easy easy everything
you touch turns to rigor mortis.
You know really with your strength I bet
you could take that radiator and just pull
it out by the roots and play it like an
accordion How would that be fun when you
can even take those bars and just
bend them apart. I don't like to for
a while go ahead Frank All right.
All of that's great mobility she your
strong do you want are there out there
reading at all that's OK well you've done
enough you're wonderful with all your
salad spinach you're great I'll buy you
a rabbit later. Thanks very
much for. That fireplace what.
We got to be cute and all. Yeah. You.
Mean. Well hey. Did you hear that.
Big detective outsmarted by an imbecile.
To get out of here and kill orders and
were caught like rats in
a trap. Well at least her
boyfriend or girlfriend. Is
your dinner. Thank you.
All you're struggling.
See I told you the snow you struggled
you know Deputy. I'll be your
nearest patient Grace
is where I don't close.
My car you can't miss it it's great convertible
job hard to call it that that it's
. You that suppose they took the key
to this track your total wires.
Coming. There's.
Been above all replicas in
the third Do you. Think.
She looks in here. There's nothing
here but this made your peace
a more space yours. Can't you.
I. How do you do my dear.
Going around to the
prisoner's side see. See.
How many branches of government.
Government consists of three branches.
What three branches of
our government. Three
branches of government are. The
legislative the executive and the.
What legislative branch of government.
It makes the whole. What that the
executive branch of our governments do
it carries out. Speaking out. He's.
Tried to help I would
totally be. Wonderful
but I don't. Take it easy kind
of. Look I was I would just.
Come here you'll coward. To try.
Oh oh nothing personal. I'll just
come here come in where are you
hey well where. Are you. Why do you.
Think you. Are.
Well you.
Know it's really good what came out.
Had to get rid of you just
couldn't stand the details B.B.
I just. Could take. At least break.
When you. Could be key to create.
The time to hit the jackpot.
You do better with your I'm not sure.
What happened Hey I'm driving but.
I'll take it through to get
a little rough thing. That didn't make
it to the city will come of the current
or better yet we'll go to you often get in
there and then we'll go to all of which
I got news for you Miss Monterey. But damn
you can apportion myself this kind of
life was too rich for my blood
a little I got left I'll get to the map now
we'll call it quits telling Mr McMahon
are you always the fate of all men
with phony southern accent wait
a minute what do I owe you all I
know is you came into my office with
a phony story no ring and oh I got the ring
and I'm stuck with the story. Put this
chap up going to raise it never rains
at this time of the year. Your
are. Born Jews. They are
Ronnie Jackson photographer baby yeah that's
me well. Spare my car he's out of town
which is
a tough break for all of us September so
you've been playing decay Yeah through
play ancestor the last twenty four
hours I've been knocked out shot
a big enough knocked out again and put
through the wringer and are still alive it's
only because the insurance company doesn't
want to give up their freight it would
break up. Here here's your map Miss
Monterey right watercooler the wrong
office Good bye. Good bye I mean.
Mr Jackson. By and I don't
mean See you later saw
sister.
Wait
a minute you can't go out like that and
you're soaked to the skin manage all steady
Why do women always act like women here do
a good thing I forgot what
you need. And once with
a laser still at the laundry. You
know it's my room over here behind
a screen you're not a detective
you act like one I lie exactly
a cream puff sister. I could
use waterways in this
business. Oh Ranney Yeah I
just wanted you to know I'm
not really angry with you I know I'm very
grateful for all you've done. Even if you
were spam accounts you couldn't accomplish
more. No red apple me from now on I'm
going to stick to watch the
birdie leave the chicks alone. I
think you're very brave man I know it's
never one card I see while. You sniff
at it no one else came
to help me. Clean No You
know what kind of a second you take me
for just because you're a girl and I'm
a boy and you're grown those big blue eyes
at me and you let me put my arms around
you and let me hold you close even closer
you think you can get me to do anything
you want. What do you want to be
counting the first thing to do are
doing it. We've got to find James.
Collins. No no we got to get out of here
this is the first place those characters
a look I don't want that kind of playing
money played on my throat take those off
watch I mean put this on. A little bit.
Just. Hurry This is Jeff and I'm very
disappointed in you I don't think of it just
then it's fine for the first
time in his life and they need
a raw deal don't worry about famous give
your money back. And money back to.
Good God. Let's go lower still here.
I'll send you check. That you
gave me the right to do yes.
My next move is to contact Mr James
Collins the secretary said he had
a date that night of the
spot called the pull
a door from here and we had no worries on
his cute little playmate they were washed
up through lost in the
shuffle while pulling
a door was our next stop but we didn't look
exactly like cafe society so I blew the
bank roll around a tuxedo for
myself and an evening gown for
a car lot boy did she stack up
I guess you only get out of
a thing what you put into it an
hour later we were at the pool
a door one of those real
swanky cafes where.
I do and been waiting. To pounce
table he's expected. To come.
This way please just a
minute but his accent still
a lot of the table over there she
wanted on the phone. To think.
You're one of the typical MS. COLLINS
We like to speak you from and
I don't believe I've had to sit out start
talking maybe my name is caught in my
pain my ankle is back to that
on Monday. I don't think I
ever my uncle told us to get in touch
with. I'm sorry but I think you
have the wrong man wait on.
This map mean anything to you.
There is the better. Hearing. And you had
a phone company I will check it for you
met him about him had an important
appointment when he afternoon in Washington
Washington to his office in the going
to town. Someone must keep an appointment
someone will but it won't be the right
Baron Montane right across moves to get
through companies that sent you to us one
day and you stay here these men are killers
and I asked you to come out and we did
not make it forty five minutes call the
police all of them check. The testing
police stations close is good work over
there but the sooner we get this in Banda
the F.B.I.
The better and. Better Monday's appointment
in Washington Wednesday was with the
State Department. Point this thing is
dynamite look Mr Collins just how do you
figure in this deal I'm
a geologist better Monday and spent Bemis
In fact I drew up this map but it shows
that location of
a great deposit of cry of
light. Yesterday morning I got
a voice exactly like better.
Said that there had been
a change in. What that means not exactly
I mean just somebody some other
government perhaps as.
Well we can get it. Containing cryptic
are all we can get that. Script about.
What. I read Buck Rogers
to you know raining.
The thing was much bigger.
What's.
OK.
Expect to get away with.
That. Driver's license. So this is my car.
I don't drive I drink
a lot I get. Well I was just cleaning
out. I wouldn't think about.
Some of my best. Fast
look suspicious.
Operational problem we
have the map. Tokelau they
brought that talent it was quite a
blow for the kid bounced back like
a rubber ball and I saw from two men I was
in the mood to play catch I was in for
keeps Now Ronnie Jackson wanted for murder.
We were going to say the Dow's Uggla
Mrs Jackson's boy we had to get some of
that gang Next up had to be washed or we
needed ot get that little car lot of came
through we got the last two seats on
a plane headed east and by midnight
we were playing tag with the Rockies
a lot of was very sweet
she looked after me like
a mother she wanted to make
sure I didn't get away and for
a disguise I was wearing
a ten o'clock shadow at the plate caging
the only thing that bothered me was the
Alex I knew it would get me I get air
sick when I step on the carpet we had
Washington about noon
the next day we grabbed
a cab for the Pilgrim hotel. This was the
end of the ride the payoff Ronnie Jackson
versus mint julep. My brain pitted against
his yeah he had the brain and I had the
pit.
They hadn't got a room I just
tossed a smile at him honey give us
a joint Thank you. Syria
thank you. And. I get so short
and breath joint and later
see about that room say but we'd like to
talk to you but I'm going to. Tell me the
number very mountainous we sorry south of
town. Mr Dawson of the State Department.
Oh yes I was expecting sweet
fourteen say thank you. Yes
we'd like
a room play something on the fourteenth
floor sorry we are but I think they want to
buy those rooms fantasy in my car and
Kelly and show oh yes would you please
register. I thought you
said you didn't have
a room when you see if you were with the
convention I could probably hear you sure
where were the convention Well
you certainly don't look like
a detective well as the.
Oh well I'm not exactly
a detective I'm more of
a stupid I'm very young I'm always shall
see and I do not have to look at.
We must be all for boys Cheerio Pip top
hole and all that sort of come to come we
must be late fifty eight oh I saw the
comfort you know the last step up but thank
you. Yes read on about it holy crap you're
a killer. You got me here we all you
gang Slayer jail in New York Mary yeah
yeah sure and I'm just
a San Francisco murderer. You know how
much more of this I can take you had me in
hot water so long I feel like
a teabag Why don't you quit I can take
it from here Oh sure now that you got me
over
a barrel now that I'm wanted for murder or
murder. You want me to quit let me. Hear
that bell ringing. Just rang
for ice water and fourteen C.
And who do you think is going
to bring up me my chambermaid.
Hey. Hey hey Mr Dawson to the parking lot
back Mr Dawson I want to tell people you
would worry that all right
Major Montague. If I. Am
a beach bag this ice water that's
a plot of fourteen it was on fire which I
thought that comedy and get these bags an
emergency she says on
come on OK So if you.
Don't push me around my dues are
paid to you. Aren't already.
Led to golf. BALL You know. That
portfolio with offices in their assignment
area they won't be back here and there
over the portfolio of New Yorkers. Eight
hours of eating I know Mr Dawson
beauty. Nice having you with.
Your view Washington or not they would
have to tell you about those NO NO
NO. Like you know the little boy no no
I'm fine all right thank you yes all by.
All by I'm sorry yes I'm not sure.
What you're going to be after
here at all and you and the other
boy are just some of your mare.
Give us your breath or thank you. A.J.
. A OK shocker.
To be proud of right now you
know kids were never proud of.
Where oh. Battens
a stubborn no man still hasn't talked he.
You pretend he doesn't know the code.
Given that.
We were very young. But really.
We're friends pals Remember
sure I like you here let's go you know what
we know they grew and everything we're
friends let's be
a little here have some wallets are
them your slippers to me Your keep me.
You know I like well much
better than almost any. Cock.
I am. They don't care and
they will. Just forget it
years I bring you some bleach
crack with your highly.
Refined.
You know who I've just seen at least
a part of Jim Colby. Should
Quit What are you doing
reckon I could go to all said he was right
I was not mean to interrupt him but I
just want to get up. To
date on Mark's way to talk.
All right so it's for
that hour keep quiet.
And he look huge but you look
to the thing and I think in
a portfolio Jeff if you're too smart to
put anything on paper. I go out there and
shoot it up for them but it's so messy I
looked up to foreign capital we've got to
get something out of maybe oh we're dead
ducks. We got here so maybe your ducks
here said that. And. What if that's
a recording machine repeats what you're
saying you know for a guy to have to hold
a secretary in his lap do you know how I
work to show you just speaking of this
Mike you make
a record that think that's what you want
in the scene I get from the top says one
of the best ideas I ever had
marvelous what you can do. OK wait
a minute. I
don't know I can't.
Call water the chamber of
a power you see she's dangerous we've got
to get rid of. We don't want the trouble
here potential trouble Hypertime to town
continued to my brother. I said let her go
all right we'll handle it.
Whatever happened to your friend well
his name Mr Jackson. You never knew
what he did. You is much.
Too weak to fight in need of.
Really nothing to fight about on
a show you what I mean. I want to make you
will not be generous offer concerning
this. Map here.
Now I'm repeating that offer the Seems to
be something missing here the cold you
give me the cold to be rainy of deposits
in Sandy much and I'll let you both go. My
uncle. Otherwise. You know what we
did to Mr Collins. We I did
our spirit coming when I
do
a job I do it I don't think we ought to waste
time arguing between ourselves he's made
all right. Very big decision I
don't like to be kept
waiting no we don't. Make
a lot of. Did you really kill to.
Think good baby photographer did for me
to take you on I had such a neat job
a big job in keeping an amateur did.
Stop taking I'm not taking any brows I'm
still waiting column. Here make. Kid
I can't believe that you killed
Mr Cullen. Can't be much.
To say. That doesn't stink
about to come out. Easy
cuddles One moment you're
a dead midget don't recognize me give
me that map maybe I want to be in
a crossfire get your friends in here sorry
I'm proud but you're so full of holes
you look up. To get them and.
Make it snappy I swear maybe
orders coming out. Every time I eat
out of the palace I got
a bullet in for each of you and one left
over in case I can still hear Brady you
know Dick's downstairs Tom give him
a party of fourteen see her it. Will be all
right all right this is my time I work
. Alone My guts are covered. Up obviously.
I said back up. OK then backed up.
Fellas be sensible
relation but. They did not
mean no harm. See just the most right
number you guys are going to do this when.
I'm well are you. Ready or not
I don't want to hurt you.
Why you can already use your pain.
How much. Does the fact
of the. Side of my.
I can't go any higher the
feeling. Is always. The
only question I want
to. PLAY THE been here
the end.
Zone. I'm going to see. One point
of my glad to say you are S.S.
Man he's
a question I'm under the ROM are. You alright
thanks you guys are just in time what
is this what they own some of them too
much stuff I won't show to me from the
direction water but the state of California
for the mother of one James Collins
just
a minute you listen to that record you'll
see who killed James Collins Yeah I get
the record will pledge to. Come
watch the snow that's coming.
I'll show you how to fix the character.
When you hear this and all these guys with
a cooler that's right Ronnie you may be
having the Texas convention but I've been
doing a little sleuthing
myself in a modern way with
a recording machine now to me that record
back away gram one gentleman the record
you're about to hear not only clears
me of a murder charge but also exposes
a tremendous international conspiracy I
conspiracy gentlemen which seeks to destroy
civilization less. With
the US. On the
record I've been framed they switch the
records I know wait a minute if I'm just
a minute before you take them away in my
truck is something that belongs to me Give
me that man. Want taste after Ascot how.
High. Let's go Kayla.
Say. Well that's about it.
You know the rest but trial for
a lot of never showing up. I still. Say
. Yeah well like early about five minutes
I'll be the late Ronnie Jackson. We get
him for this thank you Miles
remember I'm doing this for
a song. Had to take your brain so that's
what is the thing Doc is
this this is. Still being.
Well ordered. And in addition
the governor. Open up.
Come here son you and I are going to take
a little while. But it's
actually. You can test.
So much more. Now I like the tough
sleep I've. Got you took.
The last. Hour look. Come out of Columbus
if you come across or want to come to my
trial why are you banning free. And free.
The power. To do it with your own little
teeny little camera. Fantastic funny thing
dresser just like you shot
a phony bear so you're the McCoy the man
I want to thank you for saving my life.
And I didn't I knew I had a demi
A Maybe I was supposed to be
a detective and that's it Ronnie Jepson
a private eye. No I think you gotta stick
to taking baby pictures oh I forgot to
tell you excuse her solo. Oh.
We'll take any kind of
a party. List
.